Amazon Warehousing and Distribution, or AWD, is a low-cost bulk storage solution for your inventory
that distributes to the Amazon Store and other distribution channels, saving you time and money
when you have large quantities of inventory to store and distribute.
Utilizing AWD for your bulk storage can help you reduce storage costs.
By sending your inventory in bulk to AWD facilities, you can take advantage of lower per unit storage
fees compared to standard FBA.
Automate Replenishment.
AWD automatically replenishes and optimizes your inventory in FBA fulfillment centers.
Expand your distribution.
Your inventory stored in AWD facilities can be distributed to the Amazon Store as well as other
sales channels.
Plus, AWD pricing covers FBA inbound placement fees, making AWD a simplified, cost-effective way
to store and distribute your inventory with Amazon
handling the logistics on your behalf.
The Amazon Warehousing and Distribution Program supports a variety of FBA products.
When you book shipments, Amazon will validate that the ASINs you're attempting to send
are eligible.
Eligible SKUs must meet the following criteria.
Conveyable inventory with maximum carton box dimensions of 25 by 25 by 25 inches and maximum weight
of 50 pounds.
Individual SKUs inside a carton box cannot be larger than 18 by 14 by 8 inches or weigh more than
20 pounds.
Cartons boxes must contain one unique SKU each, not a mix of SKUs.
Certain product categories may also require pre-approval from Amazon before listing.
Review the Amazon Warehousing and Distribution AWD Product Eligibility Help Page to check for specific
product eligibility.
To start using the Amazon Warehousing and Distribution Program, in Seller Central, go to the Inventory
drop-down menu
and select Warehousing and Distribution AWD.
From the Program Page, click Send to AWD.
Within two to three days of creating your first AWD shipment,
you will be able to access the AWD Inventory page to manage your shipments.
There are no fees to get started.
You'll only be charged when you ship your inventory to our facilities.
Remember, the Warehousing and Distribution tools are only visible to users with permissions.
If you don't have permissions, ask your primary account holder to grant them to you via the User
Permissions page.
By leveraging AWD, you can streamline your inventory management,
reduce storage costs, and expand the distribution of your products.